var data = [{
	"question":"How many digits are there in Hindu-Arabic System?",
	"a":"10",
	"b":"20",
	"c":"30",
	"d":"40",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":" Which among the following is the largest known number in the world?",
	"a":"gramplex",
	"b":"googol",
	"c":"googolplex",
	"d":"gram",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"What does 1 googol means?",
	"a":"1 followed by hundred zeros",
	"b":"1 followed by thousand zeros",
	"c":"1 followed by ten thousand zeros",
	"d":"1 followed by 1 lakh zeros",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"Counting numbers are kept under ________ number.",
	"a":"Natural",
	"b":"Whole",
	"c":"Rational",
	"d":"Odd",
	"ans":"a"
},{
	"question":"In which number system, there is no symbol for zero?",
	"a":"Hindu Arabic system",
	"b":"Roman",
	"c":"Egyptian",
	"d":"Mesopotamia",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"p, p + 2, p + 4 are called __________ if all numbers are primes.",
	"a":"Pythagorean Triplet",
	"b":"Prime Triplet",
	"c":"Lucas number",
	"d":"Fermat number",
	"ans":"b"
},{
	"question":"Which of these could be either a circumference divided by PI or a song written and recorded by David Bouie?",
	"a":"The Tangents",
	"b":"John of Arc",
	"c":"In search of last chord",
	"d":"The width of a circle",
	"ans":"d"
},{
	"question":"Any number in the form of 2p-1, where p is a prime is known as:",
	"a":"Dual Prime",
	"b":"Goldbach Prime",
	"c":"Mersenne Prime",
	"d":"Golden Number",
	"ans":"c"
},{
	"question":"Which number has just 3 prime factors of 2, 3 and 7?",
	"a":"18",
	"b":"24",
	"c":"52",
	"d":"42",
	"ans":"d"
},{
	"question":"Mutiply XXI by II and what result will you get in Roman number system?",
	"a":"XLII",
	"b":"XXIII",
	"c":"XXXXII",
	"d":"LXII",
	"ans":"a"
}];